<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oh My Stats</title>
    <link>https://JinghongZeng.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Oh My Stats</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://JinghongZeng.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Among youths tested positive for Covid, higher risk in those hospitalized than those discharged home?</title>
      <link>https://JinghongZeng.github.io/post/2022-01-18-among-youths-tested-postive-for-covid-higher-risk-in-those-hospitalized-than-those-discharged-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://JinghongZeng.github.io/post/2022-01-18-among-youths-tested-postive-for-covid-higher-risk-in-those-hospitalized-than-those-discharged-home/</guid>
      <description>A recent prospective cohort study on the proportion of youths infected by Covid to have severe outcomes suggests that youths who tested positive for Covid and were hospitalized is more likely to have severe outcomes than those who tested positive for Covid but were discharged home.
This study only did association analysis, not causal analysis. This apparent difference may be because youths who are in better conditions after getting infected are more likely to get discharged home, otherwise they would be hospitalized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Draw a flower with XY-pic package in LATEX</title>
      <link>https://JinghongZeng.github.io/post/2022-01-06-draw-a-flower-with-xy-pic-package-in-latex/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://JinghongZeng.github.io/post/2022-01-06-draw-a-flower-with-xy-pic-package-in-latex/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I found that XY-pic package can draw complex diagrams in LATEX. It allows users to design the diagram and draw as in a matrix. So a diagram is sliced implicitly as a matrix, where each entry is an element of this matrix. It becomes easy to draw a diagram based on positions.
I saw a flower pattern on the tissues that I use everyday. So I drew this flower:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hi Stats</title>
      <link>https://JinghongZeng.github.io/post/2021-12-26-hello-stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://JinghongZeng.github.io/post/2021-12-26-hello-stats/</guid>
      <description>Hi Stats!
I really spent some time thinking about which sentence would be more interesting for the first blog. One idea is &amp;ldquo;Hello World&amp;rdquo;, but I wanted to come up with something special, so &amp;ldquo;Hi Stats&amp;rdquo;. I guess nobody used this greeting before.
I&amp;rsquo;ll share something about Statistics, and maybe case studies from another Github repository.
Then happy Stats!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://JinghongZeng.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://JinghongZeng.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Feel free to send me your ideas or questions.
Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
